(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.kisskh.xyz دعم الإدارة)
BOSS
رئيس
BLOODHOUNDS
كلاب الصيد
Fuck.
اللعنة.
Who is this guy?
من هذا الرجل؟
Kill him!
اقتله!
Get me the address
أعطني العنوان
of the woman who runs the café in the Seongeun Building.
عن المرأة التي تدير المقهى في مبنى سيونغيون.
Come here, you son of a bitch!
تعال إلى هنا يا ابن العاهرة!
Come on.
تعال.
Damn you, you fuck nuggets, man!
تباً لكم أيها الأوغاد!
We've got them!
لقد حصلنا عليهم!
Goddammit!
اللعنة!
You sons of bitches!
يا أبناء العاهرات!
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Get down!
انزل!
Fuck him up!
دمره تماماً!
You little bitch!
يا لكِ من حقيرة صغيرة!
You bastard!
يا لك من وغد!
- Motherfuckers. - Sons of bitches!
- يا أبناء العاهرات. - يا أبناء العاهرات!
- Let's go. - Okay.
- هيا بنا. - حسناً.
- Come on! - Right.
- هيا!
Thanks for coming, Hyeon-ju.
شكراً لحضورك يا هيون جو.
You saved us quite a beating.
لقد أنقذتنا من ضرب مبرح.
God, that hurts.
يا إلهي، هذا مؤلم.
Gun-woo, is that you?
غون وو، هل هذا أنت؟
Gun-woo?
غون وو؟
It's all right.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
Shh.
ششش.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
Hey, hurry up and move.
هيا، أسرع وتحرك.
Hey.
يا.
God dammit, who the fuck is he supposed to be?
يا إلهي، من يكون بحق الجحيم؟
You're so fucking annoying.
أنت مزعج للغاية.
Fuck.
اللعنة.
Shit.
تباً.
Oh, fuck!
يا إلهي!
Fuck!
اللعنة!
You fucker! Who are you?
يا لك من وغد! من أنت؟
Shut your stupid mouth.
أغلق فمك الأحمق.
Get up. Get up!
انهض. انهض!
Would you look at that.
انظر إلى ذلك!
Hey.
يا.
Who the hell are you?
من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
- Excuse me, sir. - Hey.
- معذرةً سيدي. - أهلاً.
I asked you a fucking question.
لقد سألتك سؤالاً سخيفاً.
Sleep tight.
نوما عميقا.
Huh? What the hell?
هاه؟ ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
When did I get this?
متى حصلت على هذا؟
MY LOVELY MOM
أمي الحبيبة
Yeah, Mom.
نعم يا أمي.
Gun-woo.
غون وو.
Mom, what's going on? What happened? Why are you crying, Mom?
أمي، ما الأمر؟ ماذا حدث؟ لماذا تبكين يا أمي؟
Someone wants to talk to you.
هناك من يريد التحدث إليك.
Where are you guys right now?
أين أنتم الآن؟
Gun-woo, dear.
غون وو، عزيزي.
Hey.
يا.
Mom, what happened to your forehead?
أمي، ماذا حدث لجبهتك؟
It's all right. I just…
لا بأس. أنا فقط...
I just bumped my head into something.
لقد اصطدم رأسي بشيء ما.
Your face…
وجهك…
What happened? Woo-jin, what happened to your face?
ماذا حدث؟ وو جين، ماذا حدث لوجهك؟
Oh, uh, it's just a scratch. This…
أوه، إنها مجرد خدشة. هذا...
Mr. Choi's been worried sick waiting for you.
لقد كان السيد تشوي قلقاً للغاية وهو ينتظرك.
He's downstairs.
هو في الطابق السفلي.
- Okay.
- حسناً.
I'll be back.
سأعود.
Come here and sit down!
تعال إلى هنا واجلس!
I'm sure you're all tired, so I'll keep this short.
أنا متأكد من أنكم جميعاً متعبون، لذلك سأختصر الكلام.
When I got your call,
عندما تلقيت مكالمتك،
it felt like the world was crumbling around me.
شعرت وكأن العالم ينهار من حولي.
You are my family.
أنتم عائلتي.
I was terrified… that I might lose you.
كنت مرعوباً... من أن أفقدك.
No more dangerous schemes.
لا مزيد من المخططات الخطيرة.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
Let the adults handle it.
دعوا الكبار يتولون الأمر.
- But I… I also want to help. - Gun-woo.
- لكنني... أريد المساعدة أيضاً. - غون وو.
This here isn't a match with a winner and a loser.
هذه ليست مباراة فيها فائز وخاسر.
This is a war that will only end when someone's dead.
هذه حرب لن تنتهي إلا بموت أحدهم.
You two go upstairs.
اصعدا إلى الطابق العلوي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I don't want you to ever get involved in something like that.
لا أريدك أن تتورط في شيء كهذا أبداً.
Okay.
تمام.
Now they know where Gun-woo lives, so they can't go back there.
الآن يعرفون مكان سكن غون وو، لذا لا يمكنهم العودة إلى هناك.
Take Gun-woo's mother to the shelter tomorrow.
خذ والدة غون وو إلى الملجأ غداً.
For the time being, it will be safer to stay there.
في الوقت الحالي، سيكون البقاء هناك أكثر أماناً.
Okay.
تمام.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
What do we do now, Yang-jung?
ماذا نفعل الآن يا يانغ جونغ؟
I can make this end.
بإمكاني إنهاء هذا الأمر.
It's something we should've already done.
كان ينبغي علينا القيام بذلك بالفعل.
You think you can get Myeong-gil?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع الوصول إلى ميونغ غيل؟
I'll get started moving with Du-yeong tomorrow.
سأبدأ بالانتقال مع دو-يونغ غداً.
We'll pick them off one by one.
سنقضي عليهم واحداً تلو الآخر.
Let's have a meal with Du-yeong.
لنتناول وجبة مع دو يونغ.
Uh, Mr. Oh, do me a favor.
أوه، سيد أوه، هل يمكنك أن تسدي لي معروفاً؟
Please look into Myeong-gil's men. Let me know what you find.
أرجو منك التحقيق في أمر رجال ميونغ غيل. أخبرني بما تجده.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Oh, Mr. Director.
أوه، سيدي المدير.
You're here so early in the morning.
أنت هنا في وقت مبكر جداً من الصباح.
It seemed fitting seeing as how you were coming, Mr. Kim.
بدا الأمر مناسباً بالنظر إلى أنك كنت قادماً، سيد كيم.
I operated on them myself.
أجريت لهم العملية بنفسي.
Oh, thank you.
أوه، شكراً لك.
One of them had both of his Achilles tendons cut with a knife.
أُصيب أحدهم بقطع في كلا وتر أخيل بسكين.
And the other one had all the tendons in his shoulders severed.
أما الآخر فقد كانت جميع أوتار كتفيه مقطوعة.
He had short hair
كان شعره قصيراً
and slanted eyes.
وعيون مائلة.
He was quick on his feet.
كان سريع الحركة.
And he was really good with a knife.
وكان بارعاً حقاً في استخدام السكين.
Hm?
همم؟
Yeah, uh,
أجل، آه،
I think it was a sashimi knife.
أعتقد أنها كانت سكين الساشيمي.
Shit.
تباً.
Tell Beom he needs to get to the office by 1:00.
أخبر بوم أنه بحاجة للوصول إلى المكتب بحلول الساعة الواحدة.
- Let's have a meeting. - Yes, sir.
- لنعقد اجتماعاً. - حاضر سيدي.
Things just got interesting.
الأمور أصبحت مثيرة للاهتمام.
- Finish this. - Oh, okay.
- أنهِ هذا. - حسناً.
- Sir. - Yes?
- سيدي. - نعم؟
I'm coming with you.
سآتي معك.
You stay.
ستبقى.
I'd like to help you, sir.
أود مساعدتك يا سيدي.
Min-dong.
مين دونغ.
I'll take care of it myself.
سأتولى الأمر بنفسي.
You just live your life.
عش حياتك فحسب.
But… I really want to help you out, sir.
لكن... أريد حقاً مساعدتك يا سيدي.
Listen,
يستمع،
if I find the restaurant is in ruins by the time I return to work,
إذا وجدت المطعم في حالة خراب عند عودتي إلى العمل،
you'll get in trouble.
ستقع في مشكلة.
Keep the restaurant running. That's how you can help me.
حافظ على استمرار عمل المطعم. هكذا يمكنك مساعدتي.
But still--
لكن مع ذلك--
Stay here.
ابقَ هنا.
Hwang Yang-jung!
هوانغ يانغ جونغ!
It's been so long.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
God, why haven't you been in touch?
يا إلهي، لماذا لم تتصل بنا؟
I was busy making a living.
كنت مشغولاً بكسب لقمة العيش.
Man, why has your handsome face aged so much?
يا رجل، لماذا تقدم وجهك الوسيم في السن بهذه السرعة؟
Making an honest living is not easy.
ليس من السهل كسب الرزق بالشرف.
Right?
يمين؟
It's hard to do it honestly, no?
من الصعب فعل ذلك بصدق، أليس كذلك؟
- Man, it's so good to see you. - Yes.
- يا رجل، من الرائع رؤيتك. - نعم.
I called Su-cheol and Min-su to have them look into it.
اتصلت بسو تشول ومين سو لأطلب منهما النظر في الأمر.
This is a pretty big deal.
هذا أمر بالغ الأهمية.
These guys… aren't your average loan sharks.
هؤلاء الرجال... ليسوا مرابين عاديين.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
- شكراً لك. - شكراً.
A friend in Yeouido overheard
سمع صديق في يوييدو ذلك
Iil Group purchased an unfinished hotel building in Gangnam.
اشترت مجموعة Iil مبنى فندق غير مكتمل في غانغنام.
And they got the cash from Smile Capital.
وحصلوا على الأموال من شركة سمايل كابيتال.
- Kim Myeong-gil's company, right? - Yeah.
- شركة كيم ميونغ غيل، صحيح؟ - نعم.
But why would a corporate magnate borrow from Kim Myeong-gil? I don't get that?
لكن لماذا قد يقترض قطب أعمال من كيم ميونغ غيل؟ لا أفهم ذلك.
Well, Myeong-gil probably tricked them.
حسناً، ربما يكون ميونغ غيل قد خدعهم.
- Let's find out. - Mm.
- لنكتشف ذلك. - مم.
Finally avenging our boys.
وأخيراً ننتقم لأبنائنا.
Let's end this.
لننهي هذا الأمر.
Mr. Choi gave us his approval.
أعطانا السيد تشوي موافقته.
Mm.
مم.
Back in the day, President Choi had five knifers working for him.
في الماضي، كان الرئيس تشوي يوظف خمسة مسلحين بالسكاكين.
During that time, he would lend money to corporations,
خلال تلك الفترة، كان يقرض المال للشركات،
so he often had 10 billion won or more uncollected.
لذلك كان غالباً ما يكون لديه 10 مليارات وون أو أكثر لم يتم تحصيلها.
But places like construction companies
لكن أماكن مثل شركات البناء
would always have gangs that would be looking out for them.
سيكون هناك دائماً عصابات تحميهم.
That's when these guys would go.
هذا هو الوقت الذي كان هؤلاء الرجال يذهبون فيه.
They would go out and obliterate an entire gang in a day.
كانوا يخرجون ويقضون على عصابة بأكملها في يوم واحد.
Back then, even the big gangs were terrified of President Choi's knifers.
في ذلك الوقت، حتى العصابات الكبيرة كانت ترتعب من سكاكين الرئيس تشوي.
When I finally got Choi out of the way,
عندما تخلصت أخيراً من تشوي،
the first thing Beom and I did was get rid of the knifers.
أول شيء فعلته أنا وبيوم هو التخلص من حاملي السكاكين.
And do you have an idea of why we did that?
وهل لديك فكرة عن سبب قيامنا بذلك؟
Uh, no.
لا، لا.
Because I was scared as fuck too, you know?
لأنني كنت خائفًا جدًا أيضًا، أتعرف؟
You and In-beom took them out alone?
هل قمت أنت وإن-بيوم بإخراجهم بمفردكما؟
We sent two gangs, one from Sindang-dong and one from Yeongdeungpo, as a unit.
أرسلنا مجموعتين، واحدة من سيندانغ دونغ والأخرى من يونغدونغبو، كوحدة واحدة.
We were able to do it because they weren't together at the time.
استطعنا فعل ذلك لأنهم لم يكونوا معًا في ذلك الوقت.
Otherwise, it would have been impossible.
وإلا لكان ذلك مستحيلاً.
Wow. That's amazing, sir.
يا للعجب! هذا مذهل يا سيدي.
But in the end,
لكن في النهاية،
I couldn't get rid of the two most important ones.
لم أستطع التخلص من أهم اثنين.
Lee Du-yeong and Hwang Yang-jung.
لي دو يونج وهوانج يانج جونج.
President Choi's left and right-hand men.
الرجلان المقربان للرئيس تشوي، أحدهما على يمينه والآخر على يساره.
Back when I was President Choi's lackey, I once had a run-in with Lee Du-yeong.
في الماضي، عندما كنت تابعاً للرئيس تشوي، حدثت لي مشادة مع لي دو يونغ.
He's handsome.
إنه وسيم.
This one time, a gang leader was stuck in traffic,
في إحدى المرات، علق زعيم عصابة في زحام المرور،
so he was having a smoke with his window rolled down.
كان يدخن سيجارة ونافذة سيارته مفتوحة.
He heard a motorcycle approaching, so he turned his head.
سمع صوت دراجة نارية تقترب، فالتفت برأسه.
And Lee Du-yeong carved his face like this with a sashimi knife.
وقام لي دو يونغ بنحت وجهه هكذا باستخدام سكين الساشيمي.
Fuck, his mouth was bleeding, flapping in the wind.
اللعنة، كان فمه ينزف، ويرفرف في الريح.
Shit, that's amazing.
يا إلهي، هذا مذهل.
Who's Hwang Yang-jung, sir?
من هو هوانغ يانغ جونغ يا سيدي؟
Well, they say
حسناً، هذا ما يقولونه
that he made cripples out of 20 gang members
أنه تسبب في إصابة 20 من أعضاء العصابة بإعاقات.
by severing their Achilles tendons solo.
عن طريق قطع أوتار أخيل الخاصة بهم بشكل منفرد.
I've also heard he uses two knives at once and can stab a hundred times in a minute.
سمعت أيضاً أنه يستخدم سكينين في وقت واحد ويمكنه أن يطعن مئة مرة في دقيقة واحدة.
Crazy shit.
أشياء مجنونة.
Did you say that three kids showed up?
هل قلت إن ثلاثة أطفال حضروا؟
Yes. A girl showed up about halfway.
نعم. ظهرت فتاة في منتصف الطريق تقريباً.
And I think she's somehow connected to that bookstore I mentioned to you.
وأعتقد أنها مرتبطة بطريقة ما بتلك المكتبة التي ذكرتها لك.
It would make sense if Choi owns the bookstore.
سيكون ذلك منطقياً إذا كان تشوي يمتلك المكتبة.
That senile fuck must have crawled out of the shadows to save his kids.
لا بد أن ذلك الأحمق الخرف قد خرج من الظلال لينقذ أطفاله.
Do you know how much money President Choi has?
هل تعلم كم يملك الرئيس تشوي من المال؟
I'd guess, in cash, about 50 billion.
أظن أن المبلغ النقدي يبلغ حوالي 50 مليار.
That could fully cover the money we're short on, sir.
هذا كفيل بتغطية المبلغ الذي نعاني من نقص فيه بالكامل، سيدي.
Well, I guess someone up there's looking out for us.
حسناً، أعتقد أن هناك من يرعانا في الأعلى.
Jang-do and Beom, I want you to stake out the place
جانغ دو وبيوم، أريدكما أن تراقبوا المكان
and bring me everything.
وأحضر لي كل شيء.
LOVE ORPHANAGE
دار أيتام الحب
Oh!
أوه!
Aren't you coming?
ألن تأتي؟
I don't want to go in. Make it quick.
لا أريد الدخول. أسرع.
Suit yourself. We'll be right back, okay?
كما تشاء. سنعود حالاً، حسناً؟
Kids, this way.
يا أطفال، من هنا.
Come this way, please.
تفضل بالدخول من هنا، من فضلك.
It's a children's room, so it's a bit small.
إنها غرفة أطفال، لذا فهي صغيرة بعض الشيء.
But it should be all right. Please take your time.
لكن لا بأس، خذ وقتك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
What do you think, Mom? There's Woo-jin.
ما رأيك يا أمي؟ هناك وو جين.
Hello, ma'am.
مرحباً سيدتي.
A friend from grade school works for a guy that works for Kim Myeong-gil,
صديق لي من أيام المدرسة الابتدائية يعمل لدى رجل يعمل لدى كيم ميونغ غيل،
so he was there when things went down that day.
لذا كان موجوداً عندما وقعت الأحداث في ذلك اليوم.
From what I heard, it got pretty scary.
حسب ما سمعت، فقد أصبح الأمر مخيفاً للغاية.
They were waiting at the gas station,
كانوا ينتظرون في محطة الوقود،
and as soon as that Iil Group heir came in,
وبمجرد أن دخل وريث مجموعة إيل،
they locked him up, beat him, and threatened to kill him.
قاموا بحبسه وضربه وهددوه بالقتل.
They must be the only guys in Korea
لا بد أنهم الرجال الوحيدون في كوريا
that would do that to such a powerful family.
هذا من شأنه أن يفعل ذلك بعائلة بهذه القوة.
- And? - And they got a video of the guy…
- وماذا بعد؟ - وقد حصلوا على فيديو للرجل...
But like…
لكن مثل...
This is Kim Jun-min, the sales director at Smile Capital.
هذا كيم جون مين، مدير المبيعات في شركة سمايل كابيتال.
He has six priors for fraud.
لديه ست سوابق جنائية في قضايا الاحتيال.
Used car fraud, credit card payment fraud.
الاحتيال في بيع السيارات المستعملة، والاحتيال في دفع بطاقات الائتمان.
You name it, he's done it.
كل شيء يخطر ببالك، لقد فعله.
Apparently, he served at Seoul Nambu Detention Center.
على ما يبدو، فقد خدم في مركز احتجاز سيول نامبو.
Im Jang-do.
إم جانغ-دو.
He was a cadet in training
كان طالبًا عسكريًا متدربًا
until he got kicked out for sexual harassing a junior cadet.
إلى أن طُرد بسبب تحرشه الجنسي بطالب عسكري مبتدئ.
He has no priors,
ليس لديه سوابق جنائية.
and he's the company's head of strategic planning.
وهو رئيس قسم التخطيط الاستراتيجي في الشركة.
That's odd.
هذا غريب.
Having a guy who understands exactly how the police operate
وجود شخص يفهم تمامًا كيف تعمل الشرطة
would really help them avoid police investigations.
سيساعدهم ذلك حقاً على تجنب تحقيقات الشرطة.
So, it's these two?
إذن، هما هذان الشخصان؟
Yes.
نعم.
You have their addresses?
هل لديك عناوينهم؟
Well, I have one for this guy.
حسناً، لدي واحدة لهذا الرجل.
He lives in Saseong-dong.
هو يعيش في ساسونغ دونغ.
We know what car he drives and the plate number.
نعرف نوع السيارة التي يقودها ورقم لوحتها.
We should get the jump on them fast.
يجب أن نسبقهم بسرعة.
They'll definitely catch on soon.
سوف يستوعبون الأمر قريباً بالتأكيد.
Yes.
نعم.
This one. I'll take him.
هذا هو. سأختاره.
- Let's go tomorrow night? - But how far should we go?
- هل نذهب غداً ليلاً؟ - ولكن إلى أي مدى يجب أن نذهب؟
What do you mean how far? Take them out.
ماذا تقصد بـ "إلى أي مدى"؟ أخرجهم.
I'll take care of Kim Myeong-gil.
سأعتني بكيم ميونغ غيل.
There's always someone with him.
دائماً ما يكون معه شخص ما.
And he's good at manipulating.
وهو بارع في التلاعب.
Make sure that you and Du-yeong go together.
تأكد من أنك أنت ودو يونغ تذهبان معًا.
I can just tail him.
بإمكاني ببساطة أن أتعقبه.
Do you know if there was a really big guy with Myeong-gil by any chance?
هل تعلم، من باب الصدفة، ما إذا كان هناك رجل ضخم حقاً مع ميونغ غيل؟
Ah, yes.
أجل، صحيح.
The detective agency asked for more time with that one.
طلبت وكالة التحقيقات مزيدًا من الوقت في هذه القضية.
I'll look into it more.
سأبحث في الأمر أكثر.
Who is he?
من هو؟
He's the one that threw me out the window, and he's as strong as an ox.
هو من رماني من النافذة، وهو قوي كالثور.
Sir, what will you do about the cash in the bookstore?
سيدي، ماذا ستفعل بشأن النقود الموجودة في المكتبة؟
We have to move it.
علينا نقله.
This one knows the location.
هذا الشخص يعرف الموقع.
Why don't we have the kids move the cash?
لماذا لا نجعل الأطفال ينقلون الأموال؟
The thing is, we don't have time, and we are short on manpower.
المشكلة هي أننا لا نملك الوقت، ونعاني من نقص في القوى العاملة.
Uh, those kids are no joke.
أوه، هؤلاء الأطفال ليسوا مزحة.
- They mowed down 30 men. - You saw it?
- لقد حصدوا 30 رجلاً. - هل رأيت ذلك؟
The men were all down when I got there.
كان جميع الرجال ملقين على الأرض عندما وصلت إلى هناك.
Thirty men without even using knives. Wow.
ثلاثون رجلاً دون استخدام السكاكين. يا للعجب!
Well, they're not your--
حسنًا، إنهم ليسوا ملكك--
Sir, it should be fine if they move it early in the morning.
سيدي، سيكون الأمر على ما يرام إذا قاموا بنقله في الصباح الباكر.
Why don't you give them a chance?
لماذا لا تمنحهم فرصة؟
Hyeon-ju's a smart kid too.
هيون جو طفلة ذكية أيضاً.
Okay, put it here.
حسناً، ضعه هنا.
Ah, yes!
أجل، صحيح!
Here.
هنا.
- One more. - Oh! Looks amazing.
- واحد آخر. - أوه! يبدو رائعاً.
Thank you for the meal!
شكراً على الوجبة!
Thank you for the meal.
شكراً على الوجبة.
- Thank you. - Please enjoy everyone.
- شكراً لكم. - أتمنى لكم جميعاً وقتاً ممتعاً.
- Mm. - Here you go, Hyeon-ju.
- مم. - تفضلي يا هيون جو.
Oh, thank you.
أوه، شكراً لك.
- Oh! - Mm.
- أوه! - مم.
Did you use our kimchi to make this?
هل استخدمتم الكيمتشي الخاص بنا لإعداد هذا الطبق؟
Uh-huh.
أوه نعم.
Whoa. It tastes totally different from when I make it.
يا إلهي! طعمه مختلف تماماً عما هو عليه عندما أصنعه بنفسي.
It's not that hard. I can teach you.
الأمر ليس بهذه الصعوبة. يمكنني أن أعلمك.
Cool.
رائع.
Oh, and I wanted to ask you something
أوه، وأردت أن أسألك شيئًا
about the… about the orphanage. Does Mr. Choi control the whole place?
بخصوص... بخصوص دار الأيتام. هل يسيطر السيد تشوي على المكان بأكمله؟
Uh, yes.
أجل، صحيح.
According to Grandpa, he used to be very poor,
بحسب جدي، كان فقيراً جداً في السابق.
so his dream was to help those in need when he made enough money.
لذا كان حلمه مساعدة المحتاجين عندما يجمع ما يكفي من المال.
Oh.
أوه.
So, then are you Mr. Choi's granddaughter?
إذن، هل أنتِ حفيدة السيد تشوي؟
Uh… Uh, no.
لا... لا.
I was placed in the orphanage when my parents passed away.
تم إيداعي في دار الأيتام بعد وفاة والديّ.
Ah, I'm so sorry.
آه، أنا آسف جداً.
Oh, I shouldn't have brought that up now.
أوه، كان يجب ألا أثير هذا الموضوع الآن.
No, it's fine.
لا، لا بأس.
Mm, I'm sorry.
مم، أنا آسف.
Uh…
أوه…
What foods do you like, Hyeon-ju?
ما هي الأطعمة التي تحبينها يا هيون جو؟
Well,
حسنًا،
I really like rolled omelets.
أحبّ حقاً عجة البيض الملفوفة.
Oh, then why don't you have some--
أوه، فلماذا لا يكون لديك بعضٌ من ذلك؟
Hey, where are the rolled omelets?
أين هي عجة البيض الملفوفة؟
My God, you two should have left some for Hyeon-ju.
يا إلهي، كان يجب عليكما ترك بعضاً لهيون جو.
Uh…
أوه…
Oh.
أوه.
That's right. I wanted rolled omelets.
هذا صحيح. كنت أريد عجة ملفوفة.
I'll make some more. Don't worry.
سأصنع المزيد. لا تقلق.
Oh, no. That's all right.
لا، لا بأس.
Oh, no, no. This won't take long. You just sit tight.
لا، لا. لن يستغرق الأمر وقتاً طويلاً. فقط اجلس بهدوء.
Make a big one, Mom, and make it thick.
اصنعي واحدة كبيرة يا أمي، واجعليها سميكة.
All right, then.
حسناً، إذاً.
A few.
قليل.
Okay, okay. I'll make them big.
حسناً، حسناً. سأجعلها كبيرة.
Hurry up and eat.
أسرعوا وتناولوا الطعام.
THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW GO TO THE BOOKSTORE AND GET ALL THE CASH OUT
في اليوم التالي، اذهب إلى المكتبة واسحب كل النقود.
KIM JUN-MIN
كيم جون مين
Take it easy.
خذها ببساطة.
- Did you pack everything? - Yeah.
- هل حزمت كل شيء؟ - نعم.
Jesus, man.
يا إلهي، يا رجل.
You two assemble the boxes. I'll go get the money.
قم أنتما بتجميع الصناديق. سأذهب لأحضر المال.
- How are we going to get these to the car? - We can carry them.
- كيف سننقل هذه الأشياء إلى السيارة؟ - يمكننا حملها.
No, that will take too long. Hyeon-ju, do you have any trolleys?
لا، سيستغرق ذلك وقتاً طويلاً. هيون جو، هل لديكِ أي عربات؟
Uh, go downstairs. To the left, you'll see a storage room.
انزل إلى الطابق السفلي. ستجد غرفة تخزين على اليسار.
Woo-jin and I will get the trolleys.
سأحضر أنا ووو جين عربات التسوق.
Arrange the cash on the floor while we're gone. Let's go.
رتب النقود على الأرض بينما نحن غائبون. هيا بنا.
Oh, you're a tough one.
أوه، أنت شخص صعب المراس.
Why are you taking your jacket off?
لماذا تخلع سترتك؟
Don't let him grab you.
لا تدعيه يمسك بكِ.
- Who is he? - The guy from the café.
- من هو؟ - الرجل الذي كان في المقهى.
Fucker.
الأبله.
Hit and duck faster.
اضرب وانحنِ بسرعة أكبر.
You little shit.
يا لك من حقير صغير.
Low!
قليل!
Shit.
تباً.
You bitch!
يا لكِ من حقيرة!
Stop! That's enough.
توقف! هذا يكفي.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
It's over.
انتهى.
It's okay. It's okay.
لا بأس. لا بأس.
- We have to tie him up. Okay. - Yeah.
- علينا أن نربطه. حسناً. -  أجل.
- Let's find something to tie him with! - Okay.
- لنبحث عن شيء نربطه به! - حسناً.
- Hey, go look over there. - Mm.
- هيا، انظر إلى هناك. - مم.
Ugh!
أوف!
Whoa, dude!
يا رجل!
Right.
يمين.
Wait.
انتظر.
Whoa! What happened?
يا إلهي! ماذا حدث؟
I don't know. I got in a fight.
لا أعرف. لقد دخلت في شجار.
You okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
It hurts like a bitch.
إنه مؤلم للغاية.
Why did you tie his hands to the front? That's going to come off easily.
لماذا ربطت يديه من الأمام؟ هذا سيزول بسهولة.
- Really? I don't think so. - So should I re-tie it?
- حقاً؟ لا أعتقد ذلك. - إذن هل يجب أن أعيد ربطها؟
Just hurry up and tie him. Go get the trolley.
أسرع واربطه. اذهب وأحضر العربة.
Okay.
تمام.
Hold his feet.
أمسك بقدميه.
All right. Let's go.
حسناً، هيا بنا.
- Hurry up, dammit. - Give it.
- أسرع، اللعنة. - أعطني إياه.
- Whoa. - What? I had him cuffed right here.
- يا إلهي. - ماذا؟ لقد قمت بتقييده هنا.
I guess he got out since you cuffed him to a pipe.
أظن أنه تمكن من الخروج بما أنك قمت بتقييده بأنبوب.
Looks like you should've cuffed him properly, Hyeon-ju.
يبدو أنه كان يجب عليكِ تقييده بشكل صحيح يا هيون جو.
Why you little…
يا لك من...
IM JANG-DO
إم جانغ دو
♪ I got this pain deep in… ♪
♪ أشعر بهذا الألم عميقاً في… ♪
About time.
حان الوقت.
We've run into a bit of a problem.
لقد واجهنا مشكلة صغيرة.
And the money?
وماذا عن المال؟
Don't worry about that. The money's still there.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك. المال لا يزال موجوداً.
And where are you going?
وإلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
I couldn't get in touch with In-beom,
لم أتمكن من التواصل مع إن-بيوم،
and my face is pretty torn up,
ووجهي ممزق بشدة،
so I thought I'd drop by the ER
لذا فكرت في زيارة قسم الطوارئ
before going back in.
قبل العودة إلى الداخل.
Did you?
هل فعلت ذلك؟
You should clean up your mess first.
يجب عليك تنظيف فوضاك أولاً.
Yes, you're right. I should, sir.
نعم، أنت محق. ينبغي عليّ ذلك يا سيدي.
But my mouth is bleeding badly,
لكن فمي ينزف بشدة،
and my teeth are coming loose, so I need to go--
وأسناني بدأت تتخلخل، لذا عليّ الذهاب.
Hey, you son of a bitch.
يا ابن العاهرة.
Call Jung, gather his men, and take them down now.
اتصل بـ جونغ، واجمع رجاله، واقضِ عليهم الآن.
I want these kids' heads. Don't you dare just fucking sit there.
أريد رؤوس هؤلاء الأطفال. إياك أن تجلس هناك هكذا.
You understand?
هل فهمت؟
Before I rip those kids' heads off, should I chop off yours first?
قبل أن أقطع رؤوس هؤلاء الأطفال، هل أقطع رأسك أولاً؟
I understand.
أفهم.
I do, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Move!
يتحرك!
Hurry up, get in.
أسرع، ادخل.
Throw it!
ألقِها!
- Pop the trunk. - Okay.
- افتح صندوق السيارة. - حسناً.
Push!
يدفع!
Careful, careful, careful.
انتبه، انتبه، انتبه.
Hurry, hurry.
أسرع، أسرع.
There we go.
ها نحن ذا.
Okay, we're done.
حسناً، لقد انتهينا.
Fuck. We have to get the safe.
اللعنة. علينا أن نأخذ الخزنة.
- Don't we have to hurry up and get going? - You can go ahead.
- ألا يجب أن نسرع ​​وننطلق؟ - يمكنك المضي قدماً.
How much is in there?
كم يوجد بداخله؟
Billions at the very least.
مليارات على الأقل.
I'm gonna help you.
سأساعدك.
- Hey, you go ahead. - Uh…
- هيا، تفضل. - همم...
Dude, bro, there are billions on the line.
يا رجل، يا أخي، هناك مليارات على المحك.
Go start the car and wait. We'll be there before you know it.
شغّل السيارة وانتظر. سنكون هناك قبل أن تدرك ذلك.
You have to hurry.
عليك الإسراع.
There's a bag underneath the cabinet.
توجد حقيبة أسفل الخزانة.
Okay.
تمام.
Oh shit, a gold bar?
يا إلهي، سبيكة ذهبية؟
- Pack it up now! - Oh.
- احزمها الآن! - أوه.
Dollars?
دولارات؟
- Don't just sit there, damn it. - Got it.
- لا تجلس هناك هكذا، اللعنة. - فهمت.
The number you have--
الرقم الذي لديك--
Oh my, you don't look too good.
يا إلهي، لا تبدو بخير.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
This bag is full.
هذه الحقيبة ممتلئة.
Why do you have so much money?
لماذا تملك كل هذه الأموال؟
Here we go.
ها نحن.
Hurry up!
أسرع!
These are really heavy!
هذه ثقيلة جداً!
Okay.
تمام.
Mm.
مم.
We need to call Gun-woo.
علينا الاتصال بجون وو.
Yeah?
نعم؟
Stay on my tail.
ابقَ على ذيلي.
Uh-huh.
أوه نعم.
Oh shit!
يا للقرف!
Shit!
تباً!
Can we go any faster?
هل يمكننا أن نسير أسرع من ذلك؟
I don't think I can. The car's too weighed down right now.
لا أعتقد أنني أستطيع. السيارة مثقلة بالأحمال حالياً.
When I give you the signal, step on it.
عندما أعطيك الإشارة، انطلق فوراً.
Yeah, I'll try.
نعم، سأحاول.
Okay, now! Go now!
حسناً، الآن! انطلق الآن!
Come on, get in.
هيا، ادخل.
They're coming. Faster! Faster!
إنهم قادمون. أسرع! أسرع!
I can't. The car is acting up!
لا أستطيع. السيارة بها خلل!
Push.
يدفع.
Oh shit!
يا للقرف!
Damn it. Hold on!
اللعنة! تمسك!
Hey! Are you okay?
مرحباً! هل أنت بخير؟
Whoa!
يا إلهي!
- Oh! - Here we go!
- أوه! - هيا بنا!
Push! Push! Push!
ادفع! ادفع! ادفع!
More! More! More! More! More! More!\
المزيد! المزيد! المزيد! المزيد! المزيد! المزيد!
Hello!
مرحبًا!
Hey, go to the right!
هيا، انعطف يميناً!
More! More! More! More! More! More!
المزيد! المزيد! المزيد! المزيد! المزيد! المزيد!
Step on it!
أسرع!
- Ugh, damn it. - It's done for.
- يا إلهي، اللعنة. - لقد انتهى الأمر.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
The car's dead. Get out. We need to get the bags.
السيارة معطلة. انزل. نحتاج إلى إحضار الحقائب.
Run!
يجري!
Hey!
يا!
Run faster!
اركض أسرع!